https://brucknergroup.com/privacy-policy/

Services
About
Contact
Privacy Policy
The Bruckner Group is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This applies to our wider business as well as our websites.Our privacy notice below explains how, when and why we collect personal information about who visits our website – including how we use it and how we keep it secure.
who we are
We are The Bruckner Group, a consultancy providing strategic guidance, actionable solutions, and tactical support to healthcare executives. We are headquartered at 27 Water St # 409, Wakefield, MA 01880.
how we collect information
When you use our website, including when you contact us about our products and services, we collect information from you.
The type of information we collect
We collect personal information that might include your IP address, geographical location, browser type, source of referral as well as which pages you looked at and for how long. It also includes contact information that you give us so that we can send you email updates.
how we use your information
We may use your information to improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;seek your views or comments on the products or services we provide; notify you of changes to our services; and send you communications which you have requested and that may be of interest to you.
access to information
We will not sell or rent your information to third parties.We will not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.
Learn MoreFind out how The Bruckner Group can accelerate and optimize measurable results for your organization. Contact us to learn more.
CONTACT
Copyright 2020 The Bruckner Group - Privacy Policy
